I'll get candles and
my mom's lace tablecloth.
내가 촛불을 준비할게
엄마 식탁보도 빌려오고
레이첼의 생일이니까
내가 특별히 연어를 삶을게
And since it's Rachel's birthday...
...I thought I'd poach a salmon.
What?
왜?
Question. Why do we always
have parties where you poach things?
첫번째 질문, 왜 파티 하면
항상 뭔가를 삶지?
You want to be on the food committee?
오빠가 음식 맡을래?
두 번째 질문, 왜 항상
당번을 정해야 하지?
Question 2. Why do we always
have parties with committees?
Why can't we just get pizza
and beer and have fun?
피자랑 맥주 사다 놓고
그냥 놀면 안 돼?
I agree. Fancy parties are only fun
if you're fancy on the inside.
동감이야, 그런 파티는
특별한 사람만 하는데
And I'm not sure we are.
우린 특별하지가 않잖아
You don't want it to be special?
특별하게 하기 싫다면 뭐
Fine. You can throw
any kind of party you want.
너희들 맘대로 해...
Joey, they're not real!
조이, 가짜 가슴이야!
내 진짜 가슴은 한참 밑에
있다고
I start miles beneath the surface
of these things. They're fake.
See?
Honk, honk!
볼래? 뿡뿡!
Wow, it's like porno for clowns!
이런, 광대가 보여 주는
포르노 같아
The One With Two Parties
Neither of Rachel's sisters can come.
레이첼 동생들은 못 온대
딜런, 엠마, 새논 쿠퍼를
초대해야겠어
I still have to invite Dylan
and Emma and Shannon Cooper.
- 새논 쿠퍼는 안 돼
- 왜?
No Shannon Cooper.
Why not her?
뭐랄까...
손버릇이 안 좋거든
Because she....
She steals stuff.
Or maybe she doesn't and Joey slept
with her and never called her back.
아님 조이가 하루 자고는
연락을 끊었던가
Joey, that is horrible.
조이, 그건 좀 심했다
난 새논 좋아했어
Hey, I liked her.
Maybe too much.
너무 좋아해서 문제였지
I don't know.
I guess I just got scared.
좀 무서웠거든
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
미안해, 우린 몰랐어
I didn't think anyone
would buy that. Okay!
안 믿을 줄 알았는데
기분 괜찮네
Hi, honey.
How did it go?
어떻게 됐어?
지옥의 졸업식이었어
It was the graduation from hell.
내 사촌은 축구선수로
장학금 받고 지옥 갔지
My cousin went to hell
on a football scholarship.
즐거워야 정상 아냐?
It's supposed to be a joyous occasion.
Nobody thought my sister
would graduate from college.
모두의 예상을 뒤엎고
동생이 대학을 졸업했는데
It's a testament to what a girl
from Long lsland will do for a Celica.
하긴 차를 사 준다는데
무슨 짓을 못하겠어?
What happened?
- 그런데?
- 부모님이 문제였어!
My parents happened.
All they had to do was sit
in the same stadium, smile...
웃으면서 가만있으면 되지
이혼 얘기는 뭐 하러 해?
...and not talk about the divorce.
But no!
졸업축사를 하는 도중에
싸움이 붙어서는
They got into a fight
during the commencement address.
Bishop Tutu actually
had to stop and shush them.
총장님이 축사를 멈추고
소리를 질러댔다고
더 좋은 건 뭐게?
You know the good news?
I get to serve coffee
for the next eight hours.
난 지금부터 8시간 동안
커피를 날라야 한다고
I guess we don't invite her parents.
부모님은 초대하지 말자
-How about just her mom?
-Why her mom?
- 엄마만 초대하면?
- 왜?
Because I already invited her.
내가 벌써 초대했거든
Did you ask Stacy Roth?
- 참, 스테이시 로스는?
- 그녀도 안 돼
Can't invite her.
She also steals.
역시 손버릇이 안 좋거든
초는 여기 있는데
생일 케이크는 어디 있어?
Here are the candles.
Where's the birthday cake?
We're not having birthday cake.
생일 케이크가 아니라
생일 플란이야
We're having birthday flan.
Excuse me?
뭐라고?
멕시코의 전통적인
커스터드 디저트야
It's a traditional
Mexican custard dessert.
괜찮네
That's nice.
Happy birthday, Rachel.
Here's some goo!
'생일 축하해, 레이첼
엿 좀 먹어 봐! '
Dr. Greene!
그린 박사님!
Oh, my God!
It's Rachel's dad.
레이첼 아버님이 오셨어!
Why are you here?
웬일이세요?
딸 생일인데
에비가 오면 안 되나?
The father can't see
the daughter on her birthday?
No, no, the father can.
몰론 괜찮죠
But since I am the roommate,
I can tell you she's not here.
룸메이트로서 말씀드리는데
레이첼은 지금 없거든요
And I'll pass along the message.
Okay? So bye-bye.
다녀가셨다고 전할게요
안녕히 가세요
생일파티를 여는구나!
You're having a party.
No, no, not a party.
아뇨, 파티는 아니고
친구들끼리 조촐한 자리예요
Just a surprise gathering
of some people Rachel knows.
피비, 챈들러, 조이예요
-This is Phoebe, Chandler and Joey.
-I'll never remember all that.
어차피 못 외워
So what's the deal?
어떻게 할 거지?
Rachel comes home, people pop out
and yell stuff? Is that it?
레이첼이 오면 다들
튀어나와 괴성을 지르나?
This isn't your first
surprise party, is it, sir?
깜짝 파티에 처음 온 건
아니시죠?
Hi, Monica.
안녕, 모니카
The Chinese menu guy.
Forgot the menus.
중국집 배달부예요
메뉴를 깜빡 해서요
So basically, just a Chinese guy.
중국사람이라는 뜻이죠
Dr. Greene, come with me.
We'll put your jacket on Rachel's bed.
저와 가셔서 레이첼 침대에
재킷 벗어놓으세요
All right.
That sounds like a two-person job.
그래, 시중들 사람이
필요할 것도 같군
Well, my goodness!
What was that?
깜짝 놀랐잖니
왜 그랬어?
죄송해요, 레이첼로 알고요
아직 준비가 덜 됐거든요
Sandra, I thought you were Rachel.
We weren't ready for you yet.
-You thought I was Rachel?
-Yes, because you look so young.
- 날 레이첼인 줄 알았어?
- 너무 젊어 보이셔서요
둘 다 백인이구요
And because you're both,
you know, white women.
Oh, I missed you kids.
Should I put my coat in the bedroom?
정말 오랜만이다
침실에 코트 벗어놓을까?
안 돼요!
- 제가 갖다 놓을게요
- 고맙다, 예의도 바르구나
-No, I'll take that for you.
-Oh, well, thank you.
Such a gentleman.
Thank you.
파티 분위기 나는구나
풍선들하며...
It all looks so nice.
So festive. All the balloons.
Oh, the funniest thing happened
to me on the way here.
여기까지 운전하고 오는데
도중에 얼마나 웃기는...
-I was driving
-That's great!
너무 웃겨요!
I can't wait to hear the rest,
but I have to go to the bathroom.
나머지도 듣고 싶은데
화장실에 다녀와야겠어요
Hey, come with me.
함께 가실래요?
-What?
-lt will be like we're gal pals.
- 뭐라고?
- 여자친구들끼리 그러잖아요
You know, like at a restaurant.
It'll be fun! Come on.
식당에서처럼...
너무 재밌겠다!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
이를 어째!
머리를 쓰자고
드라마라면 어떻게 했을까?
Think. Think.
What would Jack and Chrissy do?
Okay, now that your coat
is safely in the bed
재킷은 침실에 안전하게
벗어두셨으니...
다시 거실로 나오세요
We can come back out
in the living room.
Joey and Chandler, it's time
you take Dr. Greene over to your place.
조이와 챈들러가 박사님을
너희 집에 모셔가면 어때?
좋지!
Yes, absolutely.
Why, again?
한데 왜?
Because that's where
the party is, you goon!
거기가 파티 장소잖아
이 멍청아!
- 여긴 준비하는 곳이에요
- 네, 무대 뒤죠
-See, this is just the staging area.
-Right, it's the staging area.
이게 왜 여기 달렸어?
This is clearly
in the wrong apartment.
여러분은 제1파티장으로 가고
All right, you guys are off
to party number one.
And you....
숙녀들은 제2파티장으로 가요
You are off to party number two.
All right, let's keep it moving,
let's keep it moving.
어서들 들어가요
At least send some women to my party.
우리 파티장으로도
여자 좀 보내!
Okay, that's Ross. All right.
왔어, 오빠야
두 사람이 옵니다, 모두 쉿!
Okay, they're coming.
Thank you for such a wonderful dinner.
멋진 저녁 고마워
Thanks for being born.
태어나 줘서 고마워
Thank you for my beautiful earrings.
They're perfect.
귀걸이 너무 고마워
얼마나 예쁜지, 사랑해
I love you.
Now, you can exchange them
if you want, okay?
맘에 안 들면 바꿔도 돼
Now I love you even more.
아까보다 더 사랑해
놀랐지!
Surprise!
Oh, my gosh!
맙소사!
Wow!
모니카!
Oh, my God. Mom!
맙소사... 엄마!
너무 고마워!
This is so great!
Happy birthday, sweetie.
생일 축하한다, 아가야
로스! 난 전혀 몰랐어
You! I had no idea!
- 정말?
- 아니, 알고 있었어
-Really?
-No, I knew.
All right.
테이블의 음식 드세요
There's food and drinks on the table.
Go across the hall.
Right now, Joey and Chandler's.
이제 나가
- 뭐?
- 조이, 챈들러 집으로!
-Why?
-Just go.
- 왜?
- 어서 가기나 해
이상하네
Weird.
Surprise!
놀랐지!
Happy birthday, sweet pea.
생일 축하한다, 내 딸
Daddy!
아빠!
두 분 다 계셔?
두 분 다 오셨다고?
Both of them are here? Both of them?
Both of them are here?
Well, we could count again?
다시 세어 볼까?
I can't believe this!
어떻게 이런 일이!
이건 말도 안 돼
이건 네 생일파티라고
You know, this is ridiculous.
This is your birthday, your party.
Let's put them together.
If they can't deal with it, who cares?
파티를 합치고 싸우시든
우리가 무슨 상관이야?
-I do.
-That's who.
- 난 상관 있어
- 그럼 관두자
Are you gonna be okay?
괜찮겠어?
그럼 어쩌겠어?
선택의 여지 있어?
I don't really have a choice.
I can look at the bright side.
좋게 생각해야지
생일 케이크가 두 개잖아
I get two birthday parties
and two birthday cakes.
사실은 생일 플란 하나야
Well, actually...
...just one birthday flan.
뭐?
전통적인 멕시코의
커스터드 디저트인데
It's a traditional
Mexican custard dessert.
Talk to Monica.
She's on the food committee.
모니카에게 직접 물어 봐
요리 담당이잖아
방금 어떤 여자가 내게
'당신을 원해, 데니스'
Some girl just walked up to me
and said, "I want you, Dennis"...
...and stuck her tongue
down my throat.
이러면서 내 목을 핥았어
I love this party!
파티 쥑인다!
-Quick volleyball question.
-Volleyball.
- 배구 때문에 말인데
- 배구가 뭘?
네 방에 코트를 만들었는데
We set up a court in your room.
너 원래 그 회색 램프
싫어했었지?
You didn't like
that gray lamp, did you?
A woman stuck her tongue down my throat.
I'm not even listening to you.
여자가 내 목을 핥아서
아무 소리도 안 들려
- 데니스!
- 날 부르는 소리야
-Dennis!
-Okay, that's me.
Can you keep Dad occupied?
I'm gonna talk to Mom for a while.
아빠랑 얘기하고 있어
엄마에게 가 보고 올게
뭐라고 말을 붙이지?
Do you have any ideas
for any openers?
당신 딸과 자는 남자라고
소개하면 괜찮을 거야
Stay clear of "I'm the guy
that's doing your daughter"...
...and you should be okay.
모두 종이를 집어들고...
받아
I want you to take a piece of paper
Here you go. And write down
your most embarrassing memory.
가장 창피했던 순간을
적으세요
When you're not using the markers,
put the caps back on them...
펜을 다 쓰고 나면
꼭 덮개를 닫으세요
... because they will dry out.
안 그러면 마르거든요
Hi, Dr. Greene.
안녕하세요, 그린 박사님
So how's everything in the...
요즘 혈관수술 놀이는
어떻습니까?
...vascular surgery...
...game?
It's not a game, Ross.
A woman died on my table today.
놀이라니?
오늘도 한 명 죽었는데
I'm sorry.
죄송해요
That's the good thing about my job.
전 그래서 제 직업이 좋죠
제 공룡들은 오래 전에
다 죽었거든요
All the dinosaurs on my table
are already dead.
Listen, I don't mean
to be a pain about this...
깐깐한 척하긴 싫지만
... but I've noticed some of you
are just placing them on.
덮개를 그냥 닫으면 안 돼요
You want to push the caps...
덮개를 꼭 눌러야 해요
... until you hear them click.
'뚝'하는 소리 날 때까지요
건터! 어디 가요?
Gunther!
Where you going?
I was sort of thinking about maybe
난 그냥...
안 돼요, 가면 안 돼요!
지금 재밌잖아요!
No! No, you can't go!
No, this is fun.
We're just starting.
Here's your marker.
이제 게임을 시작하는데
펜을 받아요
If you want to go, just go.
가고 싶으면 가세요
아뇨, 그럼 또 악을 쓸 텐데
She'll yell at me again.
All right, I can get you out.
- 내가 빼내줄게요
- 뭐라고요?
What?
In a minute, I'll create a diversion.
내가 주의를 끌 테니까
잽싸게 문 밖으로 나가서
뒤돌아보지 말아요
When I do, walk quickly to the door
and don't look back.
-I think I need a drink.
-I'll get it for you.
- 술 한잔해야겠어
- 제가 갈게요, 뭘 드실래요?
-What do you want?
-Scotch.
스카치
알았어요, 얼음 담아서
스카치 들고 금방 올게요
I'll be back in 10 seconds with
your scotch on the rocks in a glass.
Neat!
- 깔끔하게!
- 물론이죠!
Cool.
Neat, as in no rocks.
얼음 빼고 가져오란 소리야
I know.
저도 알아요
Hello, Ross!
Where have you been?
로스, 어디 있었어?
화장실에 있었어요
I have been in the bathroom.
연어 무스가
속에서 헤엄쳐서요
Stay clear of the salmon mousse.
얼음 뺀 스카치로군
Scotch neat.
That's Rachel's father's drink.
레이첼 아빠가 마시지
Mine too. Isn't that neat?
저도 이것만 마셔요
우연의 일치죠?
깔끔한 스카치!
Scotch neat.
Would you excuse me?
잠시 실례할게요
어디를 가시나요, 아저씨?
Where are you sneaking off to, mister?
I'm getting my cigarettes.
담배 가지러
- 안 돼요!
- 뭐가 안 된다는 거야?
No.
What do you mean "no"?
See, because that's the staging area.
저긴 파티 준비실인데
들어가시면
You go in there, it'll ruin
the whole illusion of the party.
파티에 대한 환상이
그냥 깨져 버리잖아요
Take your scotch back in there...
스카치 들고 들어가세요
담배는 제가 가져오죠
...and I will get
your cigarettes for you, sir.
-Get my glasses too.
-All righty-roo.
- 내 안경도 부탁해
- 걱정 뚝!
What a great moment to say that
for the first time.
하필 왜 이런 상황에서
그런 말이 튀어나왔지?
Okay, the first person's
most embarrassing memory is...
가장 창피한 순간을
말해 줄 첫 주자는...
'모니카, 파티 꽝이야'
... "Monica, your party sucks."
Very funny.
우습네요
Oh, no! Did someone forget
to use a coaster?
이런, 누가 받침대 접시를
사용 안 했네
What?
뭐라고?
I don't see anything.
아무렇지도 않은데?
Great, I'm seeing water rings again.
또 헛것이 보였나 봐
로스, 그거 누구 안경이지?
Ross, whose glasses are those?
Mine.
제 안경이요
You wear bifocals?
이중 초점 안경을 써?
I have a condition apparently...
제 눈이 뭐랄까...
한쪽만 사용해서는...
...that I require...
초점이 안 잡히거든요
...two different sets of focals.
Do you know my husband
has glasses just like that?
내 남편도 그 안경을 쓰는데
Well, those are very popular frames.
요즘 유행하는 테잖아요
Neil Sedaka wears them.
닐 세다카도 쓰죠
I hear you can get people out of here.
누구든 빼줄 수가 있다죠?
레이첼, 로스가 언제부터
담배를 피웠지?
You didn't tell me
your boyfriend smokes.
Yeah, like a chimney.
굴뚝이 따로 없다니까요
Big smoker.
줄담배예요
Big, big smoker.
엄청 피워 대죠
In fact, I'm gonna go into the hallway
and fire up this bad boy.
복도에 나가서 이 녀석을
불살라 줘야겠어요
Are you wearing my glasses?
내 안경을 썼나?
Yes.
네
I was just warming up
the earpieces for you.
안경테를 따뜻하게
데워 놓았어요
Thank you.
고맙군
Is that one of my cigarettes?
그거 내 담배야?
네, 끝이 너무 말랐기에
촉촉하게 하느라고요
Yes, it is. I was just
moistening the tip.
She's taking the trash out,
so I can get you out of here.
쓰레기를 버리러 가면
지체없이 나가야만 해요
But it has to be now.
She'll be back any minute.
What about my friend?
내 친구 빅터는요?
Only the three of you.
Any more and she'll get suspicious.
아뇨, 셋만 나가요
한꺼번에 사라지면 의심하니까
-Let me just get my coat.
-There isn't time!
- 코트 가져올게요
- 그럴 시간 없어요!
Just leave everything.
전부 남겨두고 가요
앞집에서 챙겨줄 테니까
They'll take care of you next door.
Is it true they have beer?
거긴 정말 맥주 있어요?
Everything you've heard is true.
무슨 소리를 들었든지
모두 사실이에요
Could you guys please keep it down?
조금만 조용히 해줄래?
We're trying to start
a Boggle tournament.
우리 유령놀이를 할 거란 말야
You!
거기! 거기!
And you.
내 파티장에 있었잖아요?
You're supposed to be at my party.
And Gunther!
건터!
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐 해요?
다들 천국에... 어머!
Welcome to the fo
피비!
미안하지만 사람들이
부탁해서 그랬어
All right, I'm sorry.
But these people needed me.
They work hard all week.
It's Saturday night.
일주일간 힘들게 일하고
토요일 밤인데
They deserve to have a little fun.
Go!
스트레스를 풀어야 하잖아
가서 놀아요
You know, my party is fun.
내 파티도 재밌어
It's a little quieter,
less obvious sort of fun.
조금 조용하기는 하지만
사람들이...
But if people would just
give it a chance, it's
- 정신과 치료를 받으라고요?
- 네겐 문제가 있어
-You want me to see a therapist?
-Sweetheart, you have a problem.
You've chosen a boyfriend
exactly like your father.
네 아빠와 똑같은 남자를
골랐잖니
Okay, Mom, I'll make an appointment.
알았어요
병원 예약을 할게요
잠깐만 나갔다 올게요
But right now, I gotta go.
I gotta go do a thing.
Did you know your mother
spent $1200 on bonsai trees?
네 엄마가 1,200달러짜리
분재를 샀다고!
I felt like Gulliver.
옆에 서면 걸리버가 된
기분이지
Daddy, I really want
to hear more about this...
아빠 얘기를 들어주면
좋겠지만...
...but I just have to do some stuff.
잠시만 다녀올게요
결혼생활을 유지하려면
서로 노력해야 하잖니?
You work and you work
and you work at a marriage...
자기 보트만 신경 쓴다고!
... but all he cares about
is his stupid boat.
보트에 얼마나 손이
많이 가는데!
You work and you work
and you work on a boat.
내 도자기 수업을 비웃고
He always ridiculed my pottery classes.
And you sand it and varnish it.
사포로 닦고 광택을 내고...
But when all is said and done,
he still drinks out of the mugs.
그렇게 말했는데도
머그 잔으로 마신단 말야
요가에다
'매디슨 카운티의 다리'...
One night of her yoga
and Bridges of Madison County....
- 스카치, 담배...
- 분재, 치아와...
-The scotch, the cigarettes....
- The bonsais and the Chihuahua....
I may have only been in therapy
for three weeks now but
이제 3주째 정신치료를
받았지만...
What the hell does she want
with half a boat?
보트 반쪽으로 뭘 하라고?
Okay, okay, you can be shirts
and I'll be skins.
그럼 당신이 셔츠 해요
내가 피부 할 테니까!
I'll be skins!
내가 피부 할게요!
How you holding up there, tiger?
어때, 타이거?
우리 부모님이 이혼할 때
그렇게 부르더라고
Sorry. When my parents were getting
divorced, I got a lot of "tigers."
I got a lot of "champs,"
"chiefs," "sports."
챔프, 대장, 스포츠...
주지사라고도 부르더라고
I even got a "governor."
This is it, isn't it?
This is what my life will be like.
이거지, 그렇지?
이게 내 미래란 말야
My mom there, my dad there.
엄마는 저쪽에
아빠는 이쪽에
Thanksgiving, Christmas.
추수감사절, 크리스마스...
She gets the house, he's in a condo
my sister will decorate with wicker.
엄마는 집에
아빠는 동생이 버드나무로
장식할 콘도에 있고
How did you get through this?
넌 어떻게 견뎠니?
난 부정으로 일관했고
I relied on a carefully
regimented program...
...of denial...
...and wetting the bed.
잠자리를 적시면서 견뎠지
You know, I just
It's so weird.
너무나 이상해
I mean, I was in there just listening
to them bitch about each other.
서로가 서로를 헐뜯는데
All I kept thinking about
was the Fourth of July.
난 독립기념일만 생각났어
Because it reminded you of the way...
조상들이 서로를 그렇게
헐뜯은 것 같아서?
...our forefathers used
to bitch at each other?
It's just this thing.
Every year we would...
매년 독립기념일이 되면
보트에서 불꽃놀이를 봤거든
...go out on my dad's boat
and watch the fireworks.
Mom always hated it because
the ocean air made her hair all big.
엄마는 머리가 젖는다고
엄청 싫어했고
동생 질은 토악질 해대고
My sister Jill would be
throwing up over the side...
...and Dad would be upset
because nobody helped.
아빠는 돕지 않는다고
화를 냈어
도와 줘도 힘들다고 소리치고...
And when we did help, he'd scream
at us for doing it wrong.
But then when the fireworks started,
everybody just shut up.
하지만 불꽃놀이가 시작되면
모두 조용해졌어
You know, and it'd get really cold.
그러다 밤 공기가 차지면
And we'd all just sort of
smoosh under this one blanket.
이불 하나를 덮고서
서로를 따뜻하게 해줬어
It never occurred to anybody
to bring another one.
다들 까먹고 하나만 가져갔지
And now it's....
그런데 지금은...
Yeah, I know.
알아
Thanks for coming.
I hope you had fun.
모두 와 줘서 고마웠어요
즐거웠죠?
All right, I'm hitting the road.
나도 그만 가야겠다
Now, I've left my 10 verbs
on the table.
테이블에 단어 10개 적어뒀다
시 완성되면 보내 주렴
Be sure and send me
that finished poem.
Okay, will do. Glad you came.
그럴게요
오늘 와 주셔서 고마워요
-I think I saw Rachel out in the hall.
-Let me go check.
- 레이첼이 밖에 있던데
- 제가 가 볼게요
엄마가 가신대
Your mom wants to say goodbye.
생일 축하한다, 아가야
Happy birthday, sweetie.
고마워요
운전 조심하세요
You drive safe.
What are you doing?
로스, 거기서 뭐 하지?
I'm getting ready
for the water skiing.
수상스키 연습해요
다시 한번 안아 줘
어서 안아 줘!
Okay, big hug. One more.
Come on!
How are you?
안녕하세요?
-Where are you going?
-To get my coat.
- 어디 가시려고요?
- 옷 가지러
We'll get that for you.
제가 가져올게요!
All right, all right.
I can get my own coat.
됐어, 내가 갈 거야!
Sorry, we're on a major flan high.
죄송해요
플란이 얼마나 맛있던지
Oh, no. No, you're not
supposed to be here.
여기 들어오시면 안 돼요
This is the staging area.
It's all wrong. You should leave.
여긴 준비실이거든요
어서 나가세요
You know, just get out.
나가세요!
Or perhaps you'd like
a creme de menthe.
음식 좀 더 드실래요?
I have to be heading
toward my chateau.
그만 집에 가야지
I guess we're going back
into the hallway again.
- 그럼 복도로 나가야겠네요!
- 와 주셔서 정말 고마워요
Thanks for coming, Mrs. Greene.
됐어요
You take care.
안녕히 가세요
젊은이들이란...
Oh, you kids.
Well.
이런...
This is the best party
I've been to in years.
이렇게 멋진 파티는
정말 오랜만이구나
Thank you!
고마워요!
Okay, everybody,
it's time for flan!
플란 먹을 시간이야!
Yep! Get ready
for the gelatinous fun.
젤라틴 덩어리 먹자고
염증생길 때 나는 고름 같아
Looks like that stuff you get
when you get an infection.
Okay, that's enough.
- 그만 해!
- 레이첼, 플란 보며 소원 빌어
Okay, Rachel,
make a special flan wish.
Okay, I've got one.
하나 있어
고개 들어!
Heads up!
Wow! Those things almost
never come true.
생일 소원은 절대
이루어지지 않는다니까